(Sheldon:)Maybe it's a new planet.
(Raj:)Unlikely, but it could be
a dwarf planet.
(Sheldon:)Well, as long as it has
a healthy gravity
(Sheldon:)and all its moons,
I'll be happy.
(Raj:)Okay, the final image
is coming in.
(Raj:)And the object
we discovered is...
(Sheldon:)Come on,
(Sheldon:)Daddy needs a livable planet
he can rule with an iron fist.
(Raj:)A medium-sized asteroid.
(Sheldon:)That's it?
(Sheldon:)How common.
(Sheldon:)That's the chicken fingers
on the menu of space.
(Raj:)I kind of like chicken fingers.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, me, too.
I was stuck for a metaphor.
(Sheldon:)Come on,
a medium-sized asteroid
(Raj:)is still
an interesting discovery.
(Sheldon:)I suppose it
could end up
(Sheldon:)on a collision course with Earth
and destroy life as we know it.
(Raj:)You dream different than me.
(Sheldon:)It is kind of cute.
(Raj:)Yeah, it is.
And you know we get to name it.
(gasps)
(Sheldon:)We better choose a name
no one can make fun of.
(Sheldon:)Sir Frederick William Herschel
didn't do Uranus any favors.